I was just taking pictures, but I didn't say anything.
あんま撮ってるんですけど、何も言わなくて、
That's what it is though.
あれなんですけどね
It's cute.
かわいいね
You'll be told.
言われるっしょ
That's what I'm told, absolutely.
言われるよね、絶対ね
It's rare to see a girl who looks so good in black candy.
どんだけ黒あめ似合う子、珍しいよ
My skin is white too.
肌も白いしね
I guess I often dress like this, usually.
結構こういう格好が多いのかな、普段は
Black and white?
白黒?
Mostly black and white.
白黒が多い
Do you like a monochrome feel?
モノトーンみたいな感じが好きなんですか?
This is something like that, an overshirt.
これ なんかあれだね、オーバーのシャツでね
Do you like it?
お気に入りですか?
yes.
はい
Really?
本当に?
It's my first time here.
初めてきました
Really?
本当に?
So you went out of your way to buy it for me.
じゃあわざわざ買ってきてくれたんですね
It's cute.
かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I'm sure you can take pictures.
きっと撮ってられますよ
Go home, if you find a child like this.
家帰ってね、こんな子がいたら
If it were me, I'd go home with an offer.
提示で帰りますよ、俺なら
I've never been accused of cheating on someone, right?
俺買い方、浮気とかされたことあんまないでしょ?
No.
ないです
That's right, I cherish it.
そうだよね、大切にするよね
I'll take this as a memento as well.
ちょっと僕もこれ記念にするから
Can I take a little picture?
ちょっと撮ってもいいかな
whole body.
全身
It's fashionable.
おしゃれだね
Are there a lot of black and white?
白と黒が多いの?
yes.
はい
That's right.
そうなんだ
It suits you.
似合ってますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
My skin is white too.
肌も白いしね
It's cute no matter where you look.
どこ見てもかわいいじゃんね
This is why you went out of your way to dress up today.
これね、今日はわざわざおめかししてくれたんですね
You bought it for me.
買ってきてくれたんですね
That's good.
いいっすね
Me too.
僕もこれ
I bought it today.
今日買ってきました
We're together.
一緒だ
一緒ですね
After all, when you have things in common, you become closer.
ちょっとね、やっぱ共通点ができると近くなるよね
It's a little closer.
ちょっと近くなります
You look like you can stand being close to me.
近くになっても耐えれる顔してるね
So cute.
かわいいっすね
Look.
ほら
It's a little hard to say.
ちょっと言いづらい
I guess I'm a little nervous.
ちょっとね、緊張してるかな
Not yet.
ちょっとまだ
That's right.
そうだよね
After all, there are some good-looking guys nearby.
やっぱりイケメン近くにいるしね
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
I'm nervous.
緊張しちゃう
I have a magic trick to melting away tension.
緊張は僕、溶かすマジックあるんで
Can I do it for a moment?
ちょっとやってもいいですか?
This is the kind of thing that every woman loves when she pats the girl on the head.
女の人なら誰でも好きな子、頭撫でるってこういうんですけど
What do you think of this?
これどうですか?
Being patted on the head.
頭撫でられるのは
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好きです
Do you like it?
好きなんすか?
Yeah.
うん
To have my head stroked like this, to have my head patted like this,
頭こうやって撫でられるのとさ、 こうやってポンポンされるの、
Which one do you like?
どっちが好きですか?
Both are good, but being able to be stroked is better.
どっちもいいけど、 な でられるのがいい
Really?
ほんとに?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I'll do both.
じゃあどっちもやるよ
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's what I'm doing.
はいはいはいはいはい、みたいな感じでやってますけど
It's cute.
かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Her hair is also smooth.
髪もサラサラだね
Hey.
ねえ
I'll give it a try in about 5 hours.
ちょっと、5時間くらいしてやってみますね
Stroking your hair.
髪をなでるの
Long.
長っ
It's long, isn't it?
長いっすかね
I wonder if it feels like being stroked that much.
それくらいなでてられるって感じかな
Listen, I'm going to touch it like this.
ちょっと耳さ、こうやって触ってみるんだけどさ
How are your ears?
耳どうですか?
this.
これ
My ears are ticklish.
耳、くすぐったいですね
Does it feel ticklish?
くすぐったいって感じ?
I don't think it feels ticklish, but more like tickling.
くすぐった気持ちじゃなくて、くすぐったい感じかな
Feeling tickled?
くすぐった気持ち?
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうだね
So what about the nape of your neck?
じゃあ首筋とかどう?
My neck looks terrible.
首、やばいね
Tickling is stronger.
くすぐったいのほうが強い
Ah, so this kind of negotiation is quite a bit, isn't it?
あ、じゃあ結構こういう交渉、ね、
I'm not very good at negotiating.
交渉ばいけちょっと苦手なんすね
Well, I'll stop for a moment.
じゃあ ちょっとやめます
That's good.
いいっすね
It's fashionable.
おしゃれだね
I like how Cardi looks on you.
カーディが似合うのいいね
Now, let's move our hands to each other like this.
じゃあこのままの感じで、手を両手にいこう
This makes me happy.
これがうれしいよ、僕
Can I jump in?
飛び込んでいいですか?
I'll jump in.
飛び込みます
My breasts are touched over my clothes,
服の上からさ、おっぱい触られたりするの、
copper?
どう?
Don't you hate it?
嫌いじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
I wonder where there is raw liver?
どこがさ、生肝台だったりするのかな?
Hmm, below.
うーん、下のほう
Down?
下?
How far down is it?
下ってどのへんすか?
Sole of foot?
足裏?
Oh, in the middle?
ああ、真ん中?
Ah, the middle.
ああ、真ん中
In the middle?
真ん中、へぞ?
Is it a little lower in the middle?
真ん中、もうちょい下かな?
A little lower?
もうちょい下?
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
Which side are you on?
どっち派ですか?
Are you a moderate?
中派なのか?
Expatriate.
外派
Ah, you're an outsider.
あ、外派なんすね
Yes, yes, that's right.
はいはいはい、そうなんだ
It's cute.
かわいいね
Can you please listen to my request?
僕のお願い聞いてもいいですかね?
I just put my finger on it...
僕、ちょっと指を...
Can I have you lick my fingers?
指舐めてもらっていいですか?
Give me a little lick.
ちょっとペロペロして
So cute.
かわいいっすね
It's cute.
かわいいね
Is this connected with one piece?
これじゃあ、1枚でつながってるんだ?
It's connected to one piece.
1枚につながってる
It's like us.
僕たちみたいっすね
You don't think so, do you?
思ってないでしょ?
From here, it's connected here.
ここからね、ここにつながってますね
Right here.
ここにね
They really look at me.
め っちゃ見てくれますね
It's cute.
かわいいね
The way you look up is cute.
上目遣いがね、かわいいっすね
White looks good on you.
白が似合うね
Oh, this is that.
あ、これあれなんだ
It was in there just fine.
ちゃんと入ってたんだね
Solid.
しっかり
It was firmly in there.
しっかり入ってた
What should I do about this?
これどうすか?
This, being touched like this.
このさ、こういう感じで触られるのは
White: Yeah, it's okay.
白が、うん、大丈夫
Because it tickled me.
くすぐったからね
It looks like you can see my pants, but I can't see it.
パンツ見えそうで見えないんだね
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほど
It's normal, it's normal, it's me.
普段ですね、普段さ、自分です
Do you comb it like this?
こんなにとかしたりするの?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, I'll do it.
あ、するんだ
Is that a hand?
それは手ですか?
Is it a toy?
おもちゃですか?
Maybe both.
どっちもかな
I'll do both.
どっちもするんだ
Both.
どっちも
What are you imagining?
何想像してするの?
Things like looking at things.
見たりとかさ
Yeah.
うん
Yeah, do you imagine something?
そう、なんか想像したりとかするの?
I don't have much imagination.
想像はあんまりなくて
Ah, it's cute and popular.
あ、可愛い人気だね
It's cute and popular.
可愛い人気だね
But are there many colors like this?
でも、こういう色味が多いんですか?
Is it a lot?
多いのかな?
It looks good on you.
似合ってそうだね
Is it okay if I leave it like this and have a double piece?
このままさ、ダブルピースとかもあってもいいですか?
Ah, that's cute.
あ、可愛いね
Ah, so cute.
あ、可愛い
I keep saying that I have a cute face.
なんかずっと可愛い顔言ってるけど
About D?
Dくらい?
Is it about C?
Cくらいかな?
About that area.
だいたいその辺
Alright, alright, I can raise my butt.
よしよしよし、お尻上げれる
That culling is crazy
そのカリングにさ、めちゃ
Kucha.
く ちゃ
White looks good on you.
白が似合うね
It's cute.
可愛いね
This look.
この格好
It doesn't look like this, it looks like she's wearing her boyfriend's shirt.
こんな感じじゃなくて、彼氏のワイシャツ着てるみたいだね
surely.
確かに
So cute, underwear.
可愛いね、下着
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Are you okay?
平気?
大丈夫?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It looks like you're wearing your boyfriend's shirt.
彼氏のワイシャツ着てるみたいになってるね
Come on, just try standing up.
下さ、一回さ、立ってみてさ
Look around.
向いてみて
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
You can do some sexy poses.
ちょっとセクシーポーズが出来たりしますね
good?
いい?
That's strange, sorry.
おかしいね、ごめんね
The position of my neck is a little awkward.
ちょっと首の位置があかんないです
Further down.
もっと下
Is it here?
ここですか?
Further down.
もっと下
A little lower.
もうちょい下
here.
ここ
A little lower.
ちょい下
here.
ここ
Is it here?
ここですか?
Just a little lower.
もう ちょい下
A little lower.
もうちょい下
There?
そこか
Is it easy to apply?
塗りやすい?
Yeah.
うん
Is it going to disappear?
消えそう?
it hurts.
痛い
Take a look
ちょっと 見
Let me.
せて
By myself.
自 分でさ
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
good?
いい?
Open it.
開いて
It came out again.
また出てきた
Just like I usually do.
下さ、自分が普段さ、してるみたいにさ